This neural tube will divide into two main parts, the brain and the spinal region.
这个神经管将分为两个主要部分：大脑和脊髓
spinal.
区域。
There is first a first closure, it is really linked to this force of the heart.
首先是第一次闭合，这与心脏的力量密切相关。
And then it will be done a bit like a zipper, from the bottom up.
然后它会像拉链一样，从下往上
up.
进行。
But not like a zipper, it can do a little here, and
但它不像拉链，它可能在这里有点开放，
there still a little open, then close it.
然后又有点开放，然后闭合。
So we are there, it will do like this, it will do like this.
所以我们在这里，它会这样，它会那样。
We will study.
我们将研究。
the dynamics of brain development, of neurons,
大脑、神经元、
of glial cells, a lot of blood.
神经胶质细胞和大量血液的发育动力学。
You have a large supply of oxygen and glucose, but
您有大量的氧气和葡萄糖供应，但是
you also have very important drainage areas.
您也有非常重要的引流区域。
This is the cerebrospinal fluid system.
这是脑脊液系统。
The cephalic neural tube, we see that at the beginning, we already have a first image
头侧神经管，我们看到一开始，我们已经有了神经管的第一个图像。
of this neural tube.
神经管。
It's the neural plate.
这是神经板。
notochord and so it is the notochord again which is the inducing force for the whole tube.
脊索，因此脊索再次成为整个神经管的诱导力。
But also we see that there is, by the shape that the embryo takes, it
但我们也看到，由于胚胎的形状，它
takes the shape a little
呈现出一种
of a racket. So there is a part here where I have an
球拍的形状。所以这里有一个部分，我有一个
important feeding zone which makes
重要的营养区域，这使得
that the part here of the cranial part of the brain develops. From the moment
大脑颅骨部分的这个部分得以发育。从那一刻起，
where
它
It is maintained by the anterior part of
由前部
vascular type, you see.
血管类型维持，你看到了。
It comes to wrap around the front.
它向前卷曲。
It comes to put the heart which becomes a fulcrum, it comes to wrap around.
它将心脏作为支撑点，然后卷曲。
It will form, you see, small vesicles like that.
它会形成，你看，像这样的小囊泡。
So the ascent of the neural tube will produce here
因此，神经管的上升将在这里产生
vesicles.
囊泡。
These vesicles wrap around a fulcrum.
这些囊泡围绕着一个支撑点卷曲。
which are found at the level of the heart and at the level of the cardio cavity
位于心脏和心包
-peritoneal.
-腹膜腔。
We could say that it is almost a joint for the developing nervous system.
我们可以说这几乎是发育中的神经系统的一个关节。
At the same time, we see here that there is still a guide behind
同时，我们在这里看到后面还有一个引导
which is all around
它环绕着
which is called the amniotic cavity, which completely reorganizes the
我们称之为羊膜腔，它完全重新组织了
embryo
胚胎
towards a fulcrum which is the embryonic pedicle.
朝向胚胎柄这个支撑点。
The embryo that comes to wrap around...
胚胎开始盘绕...
around, completely, completely, the cardio cavity
完全地，完全地，围绕着心
-pleuro-peritoneal.
-胸-腹腔。
The growth is enormous.
生长是巨大的。
We see that there is a very important development here, already, which begins of all
我们看到这里有一个非常重要的发展，它已经开始，从整个
the part, which restarts another development here, and then there is a kind of succession
部分，它在这里重新启动了另一个发展，然后有一种连续性
between a growth movement, a movement, here, you see, each
在生长运动之间，一个运动，在这里，你看，每一次
time of ascent
上升
of growth here.
这里的生长。
And we will see the movement that descends to growth through here, at
我们将看到运动向下生长，同时
the same time that it
发生在这里，你看，每一次盘绕。
happens here, you see, each time the wrapping.
你看，每一次盘绕。
And we, we will now begin little by little to study in detail what happens
现在我们将开始详细研究发生的事情
Because not only are there a lot of things happening at the level of the brain, of the base
因为不仅在大脑、脑底、
of the brain, of the viscerocranium and of the whole system that is here, because all this will
面颅和这里的所有系统都有很多事情发生，因为所有这些都将
be interdependent of our system.
与我们的系统相互依存。
we will try to simplify
我们将尝试简化
and we will take as a reference point
我们将以
the developmental movement of the brain
大脑的发育运动作为参考点
from the structure
从结构上
mesoblastic
中胚层
that is to say from the cartilaginous structure
也就是说，从软骨结构上
of the base of the skull
颅底
we will also add all the movement
我们还将添加所有运动
of ventricle development
心室发育
okay
好的
and again
再次
above we will add
在上面我们将添加
all the meninges
所有脑膜
all the meningeal organization
所有脑膜组织
And we will see that at a given moment, the embryo will make a movement of flexion and
我们将看到，在某个时刻，胚胎会进行屈曲和
straightening.
伸直的运动。
And we will try to understand why this straightening happens and what are the practical implications.
我们将尝试理解为什么会发生这种伸直以及它有哪些实际
practical.
影响。
What are the implications in its morphogenesis, in its morphology that will be involved.
它在形态发生、形态学方面有哪些影响。
And then we're going to play, we're going to work with the brain, we're going to take the brain.
然后我们将玩耍，我们将研究大脑，我们将拿起大脑。
And you will see that I call it the unfolding of the nervous system.
你们会看到我称之为神经系统展开。
It's very pleasant and it's a great therapeutic tool.
这非常令人愉快，它是一个很棒的治疗工具。
It's so powerful it will help you.
它如此强大，它会帮助你。
At the same time that I have this development of my neural tube,
在我神经管发育的同时，
there is all the implication of the delimitation of the embryo that is taking place.
胚胎的定界正在进行。
It will happen synchronously.
这将同步进行。
We will especially focus on that now.
我们现在主要关注这一点。
And we will add around it each time, from these movements.
我们将在此基础上，每次都在周围添加。
Do you understand the idea?
你明白这个意思吗？
Since we have a nice specific developmental pattern,
由于我们有一个很好的特定发展模式，
with still some flexions, some things like that that will appear,
尽管会出现一些弯曲，一些类似的东西，
we will see again that at the moment what happens below,
我们将再次看到，当下面发生的事情，
it will happen at the same time as certain things, you see.
它将与某些事情同时发生，你明白吗。
And we will be able to have our reference.
我们将能够有我们的参考。
Now, we will try to properly develop the brain's little tai chi.
现在，我们将尝试好好发展大脑的小太极。
You know that this movement is essentially linked, in fact,
你们知道这个运动本质上是相关的，实际上，
It is the vascular field that is here, linked by the movement
这是这里的血管场，通过心脏的运动连接，
of the heart with simply the algorithm we saw which was
我们看到的算法只是一个差异化的生长速度。
a differentiated growth rate.
大脑发育，神经管发育非常快，这迫使大脑
The brain develops, the neural tube develops very quickly, which forces the brain
向前弯曲。
to flex forward.
这将导致我们在这里所说的头侧弯曲和颈侧弯曲。
This will cause what we call here cephalic type curvatures
我要说的第一件事是，这有点复杂。
and cervical type curvatures.
将出现的是一种扩张运动。
First thing I want to say is that it's a bit more complicated.
其次，这是一个向前弯曲的运动。
that will appear, it's a kind of expansion movement.
你看，如果胚胎仰卧在桌子上，面朝天花板，
Secondly, it's a forward flexion movement.
它做的第一件事就是这样向我生长。
You see, the embryo, if it's lying on the table facing the ceiling,
我有一个扩张。
the first thing it does, it grows towards me like that.
其次，由于差异化的生长速度，
I have an expansion.
前面的部落减速，
Secondly, by the differential growth rate,
胚胎做了一个向前弯曲的运动。
the horde in front slows down,
它在这里弯曲。
and the embryo makes a forward flexion movement.
我们看到这里出现了一个弯曲。
It bends here.
这里将出现的弯曲，颈部弯曲和头部弯曲，你
And we see a flexion appearing here.
看，它开始这样做，弯曲在这里继续，它继续，
flexion that will appear here, the cervical flexion and the cephalic flexion, you
在某个时刻，大脑
see
在这里，在它的发育过程中，它来到心脏上，它
that it starts to do that, the flexion continues here, it continues and
来到心脏上，后面这里
at a given moment the brain
神经管继续生长，所以这里有一个制动，你
here in its development, it comes on the heart, it
看，并且
comes on the heart and behind here
我有一个向后的推力。
the neural tube continues to grow, so I have a brake here that is created, you
在生长中继续。
This posterior thrust creates an angle above, here,
这种向后的推力在这里上方形成一个角度，
which we will call the pontine curvature.
我们称之为脑桥弯曲。
This pontine curvature, at some point,
这个脑桥弯曲，在某个时刻，
the system continues to grow,
系统继续生长，
and there, if I put it now face on,
如果我现在把它放在前面，
at first, it looks like this,
最初，它看起来像这样，
and this prosencephalon will begin to form two vesicles from the front.
而这个前脑将开始在前面形成两个囊泡。
this, you see, what we call the bulges of the
你看，这就是我们所说的脑泡，
telencephalon. I repeat, I
大脑。我重复一遍，我
have an ascent of
的神经管上升，
my tube, I have flexion and we see a cephalic flexion appear. It
我有了屈曲，我们看到出现了头屈。它
continues, at the same time
继续，同时
in this cephalic flexion I have a cervical flexion. The tube continues to push
在这个头屈中，我有一个颈屈。神经管继续向后
behind,
生长，
you see here, it meets...
你看到这里，它遇到了……
heart and there is an appearance that we call the pontine flexion that appears,
心脏，然后出现了一个我们称之为脑桥屈曲的现象，
it
它
continues to grow and there we see at that moment what we call the
继续生长，然后我们看到出现了我们所说的
process
端脑化
of telencephalization, this process of telencephalization goes
过程，这个端脑化过程在某个时刻向后
at a given moment backwards
发展，
like this, so I have this movement, I see my
像这样，所以我有了这个运动，我看到我的
little embryo growing here, flexion
小胚胎在这里生长，屈曲
Cephalic flexion, cervical flexion, pontine flexion,
头屈、颈屈、脑桥屈，
telencephalization that develops to reach a complete development
端脑化发展，以达到我的胚胎的完全
of my embryo.
发育。
Neural tube, we see that it is first the prosencephalon, then the
神经管，我们看到它首先是前脑，然后是
mesencephalon, then the rhombencephalon.
中脑，然后是菱脑。
The prosencephalon will become the telencephalon and the diencephalon.
前脑将成为端脑和间脑。
and there we see the diencephalon.
然后我们看到间脑。
Then we see here the structure
然后我们在这里看到结构
which was the mesencephalic structure
那是中脑结构
which will become the mesencephalon here.
它将成为这里的中脑。
And then the posterior structure too
然后是后部结构
which will form, if you like,
它将形成，如果你愿意，
the myelencephalon,
延髓，
here, there,
在这里，
and the metencephalon.
和后脑。
We will especially focus our attention
我们将主要关注
on this dynamic here.
这里的这种动态。
Because that's the key we need to find.
因为那是我们必须找回的钥匙。
This key here.
这把钥匙就在这里。
At that moment, already, the heart, we are already, at this stage,
在那一刻，心脏，我们已经，在这个阶段，
we are already around the 23rd day, 23rd, 24th day.
我们已经到了第23天左右，第23、24天。
That means that at that moment, the heart is already beating very strongly.
这意味着在那一刻，心脏已经跳动得很厉害了。
So already, in the brain, what can I see in its development phase?
那么，在大脑中，我能看到它的发展阶段是什么？
At the beginning, it's a, it's just
最初，它只是一个，它只是
a disk.
一个圆盘。
2 it becomes a groove, 3 it becomes a groove that begins to close,
2 它变成一个凹槽，3 它变成一个开始闭合的凹槽，
4 it begins to expand very strongly at the cephalic level,
4 它开始在头部区域非常强烈地扩张，
then it makes a forward flexion movement, there, at the same time it
然后它向前弯曲，同时它
makes a cervical flexion movement,
进行颈部屈曲运动，
I reach a point, it continues to grow, and there it makes a posterior fold at the rhombencephalic level
我达到一个点，它继续增大，然后它在菱脑区域形成一个后部堆积
to form the pontine curvature, you see,
形成脑桥弯曲，你看到了吗？
and then...
然后...
behind the telencephalon itself begins to open, it pushes but there it no longer has
在后面，端脑开始打开，它在生长，但它没有更多的
space to go
空间向前发展，它做了什么？它向后退，我们将看到。
forward and what does it do, it goes back and we will see that. The
三个脑泡，
three encephalons,
中脑、菱脑和脊髓
mesencephalon, rhombencephalon and the spinal canal.
管。这个菱脑在生长，两边各有一个，它们都开始生长。
This rhombencephalon grows and there are two of them
横向地，在某个时刻，它在前面有一个制动，通过心脏，通过
on each side and it starts to grow from both.
第一个发育的系统，然后也通过一个浓缩，但在
laterally and at some point it has a brake in front via the heart via the
化学上，它经历了巨大的扩张
first system that develops and then also via a concentration but in
它做了一个这样的运动，但它不能再
chemistry and it takes an enormous expansion
往那边走了，突然之间，
it made a movement like this but there it can no longer go
在后面发生的事情是，我达到了一个平衡状态，你看到了吗？也就是说，我不能再弯曲了
that way and all
因为我达到了一个平衡状态
of a sudden what happens is that posteriorly I reach a state of
在流体力学平面上的后部
equilibrium you see that is to say I can no longer flex
我现在要开始
because I have reached a state of equilibrium
突然之间
posterior on a hydrodynamic plane
囊泡，它在做什么？
that I will start now
它开始这样做。
all of a sudden
我长大了。
What do I become?
我变成了什么？
I become my hemispheres.
我变成了我的大脑半球。
He leaves.
它离开了。
and begins to make this dynamic movement
并开始做这种动态运动
and we
我们
see here
在这里看到
really the pattern, almost the path
真正的模式，几乎是轨迹
of its development here
它在这里的发展
an H-point
一个H点
with a fulcrum
有一个支点
with a reference point
有一个参考点
for this rotation
用于这种旋转
already what we will call
我们已经称之为
in the structure now called
现在我们称之为的结构中
the insula
脑岛
they are hard
它们很硬
of place the cervical flexion and the flexion an adaptation to
颈部屈曲和屈曲适应环境，因为有一个止动点，在某个时刻，我真的有这种向前的生长，你看到了吗？
the environment because
环境，因为
there is this stop that at one point, there, I really have this growth at
有一个止动点，在某个时刻，我真的有这种向前的生长，你看到了吗？
the front, you see
前面，你看到了吗？
and there what we see is that it continues to grow now here I
那么我们看到了什么呢？它继续生长。现在我在这里有一个制动。
have a brake
我有一个制动。
here but at the same time what happens is that the brain here you see knows very well
我在这里，但同时发生的是，大脑在这里，你看，它非常清楚
the
它
It receives rhythmic information here.
它接收到这里有节奏的信息。
Then, it develops.
然后，它发展起来。
I want, I'm hungry, I eat.
我想要，我饿了，我吃。
I want to grow.
我想长大。
Here, behind, the pontine curvature closes.
在这里，后面，脑桥的裂缝闭合了。
What will form there?
那里会形成什么？
What will it be at the level of the rhombencephalon?
在菱脑层面会是什么？
The cerebellum.
小脑。
And what will that curvature give?
那这个突起会变成什么？
The tentorium.
等待。
It is a balance between the ascent of the neural tube and the fulcrum on the
这是神经管上升与心脏支点之间的平衡。
heart.
心脏。
Another image that I like, because it allows us to already have a precise segmentation
我喜欢的另一张图片，因为它让我们能够精确地分割
of what we will call the processes of the telencephalon,
我们称之为端脑过程的东西，
and then all the migration at the level of what we will call the rhombencephalon.
然后是菱脑层面的所有迁移。
So the rhombomeres, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
所以菱脑节，1、2、3、4、5、6。
seven, eight, which are there.
七、八，就在那里。
And then we see here well
然后我们在这里清楚地看到
the backward development
这个过程向后
of this process.
的发展。
We go into details
我们进入了可以找到的
specifics that can be found.
具体细节。
Here, we will now see
在这里，我们现在将看到
again these different
这个管子的
flexions of this tube
不同弯曲，
between the 28th and 40th
在第28天到第40天之间，
day, I have this development.
我有了这个发展。
Around the 8th
到第8周，
week, between the 11th
在第11周和这里之间，
and here, you see,
你看，
I think.
我想。
I start to really have this pontine flexure that starts to be well defined here.
我开始真正看到这个脑桥弯曲在这里被很好地定义。
And then here, I start to really have the development of my telencephalon
然后在这里，我开始真正看到我的端脑发展，
which comes completely above everyone else.
它完全覆盖了所有人。
And on top of that, we take again here with the growth
在此基础上，我们再次看到神经管
important at the level of the neural tube,
的重要生长，
the mesencephalic flexion, the cervical flexion.
中脑弯曲，颈部弯曲。
Then we see the meeting here.
然后我们看到这里的交汇点。
which will give us the pontine flexion with the growth here and the development here.
这将给我们带来脑桥弯曲，伴随着这里的生长和这里的发展。
And then, posteriorly, we will have the whole process of telencephalization
然后，在后部，我们将看到整个端脑化过程，
which comes to completely wrap, with each time here, you see,
它完全包裹着，每次在这里，你看，
a concentration at some point of energy that will happen here,
在某个时刻，能量会在这里集中，
concentration of points, and we can also say that the balance point,
点的集中，我们也可以说平衡点，
the equilibrium point, the each point,
平衡点，每个点，
for the development of the telencephalon,
对于端脑的发展，
we will find it at the level...
我们将在……找到它。
So we see here the insula, it's a lobe in fact.
所以我们在这里看到脑岛，它实际上是一个脑叶。
It's the insular lobe that's here.
它是这里的岛叶。
Here we have a bit of the parameter diagram,
这里我们有一个参数图，
you see, with the global flexion,
你看，伴随着整体弯曲，
and then we see all these points that will,
然后我们看到所有这些点，
the three flexions that will.
所有这三个弯曲。
The importance here of this movement,
这里这个运动的重要性，
all of a sudden straightening.
突然的矫正。
So there will also be certain synchronicities.
所以也会有一些同步性。
We see that the flexion...
我们看到屈曲...
cephalic, here, will be in agreement with the tip of my notochord,
脑部，在这里，将与我的脊索尖端一致，
the fulcrum.
支撑点。
The cervical flexion will be in relation to the supraocciput, while
颈部屈曲将与枕骨上部相关，而
the flexion
屈曲
pontine will be in relation to the occipital base. And the telencephalic flexion
连续的将与枕骨基部相关。而屈曲
telencephalic
端脑
will be on the movement of my sphenoids, of my pre-sphenoids.
将与我的蝶骨、我的前蝶骨的运动相关。
If I am my prosencephalon.
如果我就是我的前脑。
I come forward, hop, I arrive, and hop, and there
我向前，咻，我到了，咻，然后突然间，
all of a sudden, I go back.
我突然向后退。
The celsus neurocranium or which is equal to what we call the process
大脑神经颅或等于我们所说的
of cerebralization.
脑化过程。
And at the same time, posteriorly, I have a change at the level of my primitive sclerotomes
同时，在后方，我的原始生骨节发生了变化，
which reach a state of densification.
它们达到了致密化的状态。
That is to say that I have reached...
也就是说我达到了...
and there, it happens at the same time
而这，是在同一时间发生的，
that I can start to straighten up like that.
我可以开始像这样直起身子。
I can leave.
我可以走了。
At the same time, my whole system,
在同一时间，我所有的系统，
what we call the anterior midline.
我们称之为前中线。
Look what they do.
看看它们做了什么。
Everything moves towards the midline.
一切都向中线靠拢。
By this process,
通过这个过程，
everything that is closed here
这里所有封闭的东西
starts to come back towards the midline.
开始回到中线。
This is how this anterior midline
这就是这条前中线
starts to form.
开始形成的方式。
It is linked to the process of tightening.
这与收紧过程有关。
and to the process of descent of the visceral system.
以及内脏系统下降的过程。
So I have a visceral fulcrum and I have a tension towards the other.
所以我有一个内脏支撑点，我有一个向另一个方向的张力。
This is the first movement and we will see that in
这是第一个运动，我们将看到，在
this development,
这个发展中，
afterwards we will add the base of the skull,
之后我们将添加颅底，
then we will add the ventricles that will follow this development
然后我们将添加将跟随这个发展的脑室，
and then we will add all the membranes behind.
然后我们将在后面添加所有的膜。
all the organization, all the compartment of my dura mater,
所有的组织，我所有的硬脑膜隔室，
membranes, etc., falx cerebri, tentorium cerebelli, etc.
膜等等，大脑的镰，大脑的幕等等。
And then we will add the dural sheaths again
然后我们还将添加硬脑膜鞘
to make the vault.
来形成颅顶。
The very first movement is an expansion.
Le tout premier mouvement, c'est une expansion.
It grows.
Ça grandit.
If it doesn't grow, what could it be?
Si ça ne grandit pas, qu'est-ce que ça peut être ?
A deficit?
Un déficit ?
vascular. Don't forget that the system here is also magnetic force, electromagnetic,
vasculaire.  N 'oubliez  pas  que  le  système  ici  c 'est  aussi  de  la  force  magnétique,  électromagnétique,
energetic. It grows, it comes towards
énergétique.  Ça  grandit,  il  vient  vers
you and it grows towards you. Does it grow? Okay. Then
vous  et  ça  grandit  vers  vous.  Est -ce  que  ça  grandit  ?  Ok.  Puis
it makes a forward flexion movement. The brain develops, it makes a movement
ça  fait  un  mouvement  de  flexion  vers  l 'avant.  Le  cerveau  se  développe,  ça  fait  un  mouvement
of
de
vesicle forward, it comes towards the heart like that. But at the same time, behind,
vésicule vers l'avant, ça vient vers le cœur comme ça. Mais en même temps, derrière,
posteriorly, I have a flexion.
postérieurement, j'ai une flexion.
cephalic flexion
flexion céphalique
and behind I have a cervical flexion
et derrière j'ai une flexion cervicale
at the same time at the level of my fingers
en même temps au niveau de mes doigts
behind it continues to push
derrière ça continue à pousser
and there I start to have
et là je commence à avoir
what we call the flexion
ce qu'on appelle la flexion
pontine that appears
pontine qui apparaît
at the level of my hands here
au niveau de mes mains ici
behind I have an expansion
derrière j'ai une expansion
enormous of my
énorme de mon
prosencephalon that comes
prosence céphale qui vient
and makes a whole movement
et qui fait tout un mouvement
of
de
cerebralization
cérébralisation
telencephalization that I recover at the occipito-temporal level.
délencéphalisation  que  je  récupère  au  niveau  occipito
-temporal.
-temporel.